Sara Jimena Garzón Ariza

BILINGUAL RECRUITER

+57 3057581525

sara.garzon@solvoglobal.com

Bogotá, Colombia

LinkedIn

Gustavo Ortega (Crehana) - 2022

I am a psychologist with a passion for my profession. Also, I have completed courses related to the hunting, recruiting and HR processes; I'm excited to keep practicing in these areas. I have work with people from many countries in at least three of my jobs and I enjoy learning from them. I have skills for teamwork, problem solving and communication. I identify myself on a personal level as someone with aptitudes to maintain a good management of interpersonal relationships, to be responsible, efficient, respectful, and with enthusiasm regarding putting into practice my acquired knowledge in a beneficial way for others and for my own learning and experience.

EDUCATION

Bachelor´s Degree in Psychology Bogotá, 2013-2018.

El Bosque University

Master in Criminology: Crime and victimology

Valencia (remote), 2019-2021. Universidad internacional de Valencia

Courses

Human resources administration

SENA - 2022 Community Management for beginners

HR Hunting

Martin Gerding (Crehana) - 2022

Hiring Managers: How to interview a candidate

Martin Arenas (Crehana) - 2022

INTERNSHIP

PRISON PSYCHOLOGY - INPEC. 2017.

(Instituto Nacional Penitenciario y Carcelario - Cárcel Modelo).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bilingual Recruiter July 2022 - present

Solvo Global

Recruitment and selection of human talent for companies in the United States through the management of social networks

Bilingual Agent - Teleperformance Mar 2021- Dec 2021

I was a customer service agent for a communication company located on the U. S.

Supervisor / Invigilator / Administrative assistant - International House Bogotá Sep 2018 - Present

I've been invigilator, guiding the IELTS sessions, working in customer service for the test takers. Also, I've been in charge of those sessions as supervisor and even several at once, leading the invigilators and solving any problem that may happen during the test. And I have been working in the administrative task required before and after the test until results are released.

Volunteer - Yad Hashmona (abroad) Jan 2019 - Mar 2019

Volunteer in a Hotel Kibbutz, in the areas of restaurant and housekeeping. During the volunteering I was surrounded by people from all over the world, and worked with them

Analyst - La Modelo prison, Bogotá. 2017

During my internship I was an analyst for the psychological concept related to intern's permissions and security phase change (from high to medium security, from medium to low security and from low security to house arrest).

Soft skills

- Teamwork skills
- Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking
- Empathic
- Active listener
- Creativity
- Creativity
 Decision making
- Resourcefulness
- Persuasion
- Adaptability
- Communication and interpersonal skills

Hard Skills

- Planning and management in education
- Microsoft office
- Writing skills
- · Language skills
- Photography
- Design
- Administrative organization
- First aid
- People management

SKILLS

Languages

- English level C1
- Native Spanish